<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Graph>
	<NodeList>
	<Node>
		<dialogue>
			<line>Mayor - What do you want boy?</line>
			<line>Clyde - I need to speak to you about something really important!</line>
			<line>Mayor - Unfortunately, we're stacked in paperwork. I think you should send us an e-mail explaining your issues.</line>
			<line>Clyde - This can't be discussed through an e-mail!! You have to let me explain to you, it's URGENT!</line>
			<line>Mayor - Urgent is this law about gay parents having kids, this can divide a Nation. What else can be so problematic?</line>
			<line>Clyde - This can mean the END OF THE PLANET EARTH!!</line>
			<line>Mayor - ...</line>
			<line>Mayor - AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH WHAT? Well, I really need a break from this crap, I guess you can distract me a bit.</line>
			<line>Mayor - Tell me then what happened that is sooooo terrifying.</line>
      <line>Clyde - It's ABADDON...</line>
			<line>Mayor - Ahahahah oh lord! ABA... Who? Please, don't waste my time with this invention of yours.</line>
			<line>Mayor - I'm going to call a security to lead you to the door</line>
      <line>  </line>
		</dialogue>

	  <!-- FIRST DECISION -->

    <optionList>
			<option>
				<text> 1) Did you think you can be the face of the TAKE DOWN of ABADDON?
				</text>
				  <score>1000</score>
  			  <factionArmy>5</factionArmy>
          <factionChurch>0</factionChurch>
        	<factionPolitics>10</factionPolitics>
				<Node>
					<dialogue>
						<line>Mayor - You're not joking, I can see...</line>
            <line>Clyde - You can be the most powerful man on Earth, you can have anyone respecting you.</line>
					</dialogue>
				</Node>
			</option>
			<option> 
				<text> 2) You have to HELP ME, we need to do something about Him!
				</text>
				  <score>0</score>
  			  <factionArmy>0</factionArmy>
			    <factionChurch>0</factionChurch>
        	<factionPolitics>5</factionPolitics>
				<Node>
					<dialogue>
						<line>Mayor - Do what?</line>
            <line>Clyde - I don't know, but you're the LEADER od Dabot County!</line>
					</dialogue>
				</Node>
			</option>
			<option>
				<text> 3) JOIN ME and ABADDON. You're life can be spared.
				</text>
				  <score>0</score>
  			  <factionArmy>0</factionArmy>
          <factionChurch>-10</factionChurch>	
          <factionPolitics>0</factionPolitics>
				<Node>
					<dialogue>
						<line>Mayor - Wow, okay... That doesn't make any sense. </line>
					</dialogue>
				</Node>
			</option>
      <option>
        <text> 4) *mumbles*...
        </text>
        <Node>
          <dialogue>
            <line>Mayor - Now you decided to stay quiet?! </line>
          </dialogue>
        </Node>
      </option>
		</optionList>
	</Node>
	<Node>
		<dialogue>
			<line>Mayor -  Security, wait...! Let the man speak. Tell me more about that...</line>
			<line>  </line>
		</dialogue>

	  <!-- SECOND DECISION -->

    <optionList>
      <option>
        <text> 1) I can give you 1 MILLION DOLLARS, if you HELP ME...
        </text>
        <score>2500</score>
        <factionArmy>2</factionArmy>
        <factionChurch>2</factionChurch>
        <factionPolitics>10</factionPolitics>
        <Node>
          <dialogue>
            <line>Mayor - MILLION?? Like with six 0's?</line>
            <line>Clyde - Correct!!</line>
            <line>Mayor - It will be hard, but for that ammount... </line>
          </dialogue>
        </Node>
      </option>
			<option> 
				<text> 2) Help us DEFEATING Abaddon and we'll give you a LOT of MONEY.
				</text>
				  <score>20000</score>
          <factionArmy>5</factionArmy>
          <factionChurch>0</factionChurch>		
          <factionPolitics>10</factionPolitics>
				<Node>
					<dialogue>
						<line>Mayor - That task is as hard as profitable! It's being rewarded FIGHTING for the good side...</line> 
					</dialogue>
				</Node>
			</option>
      <option>
        <text> 3) There's a BIG MONEY PRIZE waiting for you... If you're on Abaddon's SIDE.
        </text>
        <score>0</score>
        <factionArmy>0</factionArmy>
        <factionChurch>-2</factionChurch>
        <factionPolitics>-10</factionPolitics>
        <Node>
          <dialogue>
            <line>Mayor - What? Abaddon doesn't exist... I never saw him</line>
          </dialogue>
        </Node>
      </option>
      <option>
        <text> 4) *mumbles*...
        </text>
        <Node>
          <dialogue>
            <line>Mayor - Now you decided to stay quiet?! </line>
          </dialogue>
        </Node>
      </option>
		</optionList>
	</Node>
	<Node>
		<dialogue>
			<line>Clyde - Well, I think I have said enough. Now, it's up to you!</line>
			<line>Mayor - Uhm... Okay okay, you'll hear from me, I promise. Thanks for your coming.</line>
		</dialogue>
	</Node>
</NodeList>
</Graph>
